Karly Maruyama

karlypaige@yahoo.com (415)690-5299 San Diego, CA

FULL STACK PROGRAMMER

https://github.com/karlypaige https://www.linkedin.com/in/karly-maruyama https://karlypaige.github.io/Responsive/index.html

Summary

Full Stack Candidate highly adaptable, self-motivated and goal-oriented professional committed to pursuing a long-term career in Data and Computer Science. Offer a 20-year track record demonstrating strong analytical and problem-solving skills, computer proficiency, and ability to follow through with projects from inception to completion.

Skills

Advanced: HTML, CSS, Javascript, Jquery, logic and reasoning, data visualization and analysis, organization and teamwork Proficient: Python, SQLite, MySQL, C/C++, Java, php, node.js, React Expert: visual communication, creative problem solving and strategic thinking

Recent Projects

Illustration web page:

https://karlypaige.github.io/Responsive/index.html

Analysis of UCI Machine Learning Repository Hypothyroid Data Set:

https://github.com/karlypaige/Fundamentals-Capstone-Hypothyroid

Education

UNIVERSITY OF CALIFORNIA, SAN DIEGO EXTENSION

2021

CODING BOOTCAMP, FULL STACK FLEX - in progress

- HTML5, CSS3, Javascript, Jquery, Node.js, MySQL, and React.
- Fast-paced, immersive, collaborative coding program

UNIVERSITY OF CALIFORNIA, SAN DIEGO EXTENSION

Front End Development Certificate - in progress.

HTML, CSS3, Javascript

UNIVERSITY OF CALIFORNIA, SAN DIEGO EXTENSION

2015

Life Sciences Information Technology Certificate

Object oriented programming rooted in C/C++, Java, Biostatistics, Machine Learning and Pattern Recognition

UNIVERSTIY OF CALIFORNIA, SANTA CRUZ EXTENSION

2006

Science Illustration Graduate Certificate

• Clear, concise, effective visual communication in both traditional mediums: pencil/ink, color pencil, water color, acrylic, etc. and digital mediums: Adobe Creative Suite: Photoshop, Illustrator, Dreamweaver, InDesign

UNIVERSITY OF CALIFORNIA, DAVIS

1999

BS Physiology, (Minor in Studio Art)

- Focus on Comparative Physiology, Neuroscience and Behavior
- Education Abroad Program to Wollongong Australia (1 year)

Employment History

DART NEUROSCIENCE

San Diego, CA

Associate Scientist III - Department of Cellular Biology

Jan 2017 - Feb 2018

 In Vitro models of cortical neural signaling mechanisms related to memory and learning in primary neuronal cell cultures.

Associate Scientist III – Department of NeuroGenetics

Jul 2015 - Dec 2016

Associate Scientist II – Department of NeuroGenetics

Jun 2011 - Jun 2015

In Vivo models of learning and memory.

UNIVERSITY OF CALIFORNIA, SAN DIEGO

San Diego, CA

Research Associate - Department of Cancer Research

Mar 2010 - Mar 2011

• Orthotopic and genetic mouse models of pancreatic cancer research.

More employment and References upon request.

2021